<resources>
    //questionnairePage strings
    <string name="app_name">guardifySG</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="age_group">Age Group</string>
    <string name="budget">Budget</string>
    <string name="existing_insurance_you_own">Existing Insurance You Own</string>
    <string name="life_insurance">Life Insurance</string>
    <string name="disability_insurance">Disability Insurance</string>
    <string name="integrated_shield_plan">Integrated Shield Plan</string>
    <string name="accident_insurance">Accident Insurance</string>
    <string name="type_of_coverage_required">Type Of Coverage Required</string>
    <string name="how_long_are_you_looking_to_cover">How long are you looking to cover?</string>
    <string name="monthly_expenditure_estimate">Monthly Expenditure Estimate</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>

    <string-array name="gender_array">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="age_array">
        <item>0 to 19</item>
        <item>20 to 24</item>
        <item>25 to 29</item>
        <item>30 to 34</item>
        <item>35 to 39</item>
        <item>40 to 44</item>
        <item>45 to 49</item>
        <item>50 to 54</item>
        <item>55 to 59</item>
        <item>60 to 64</item>
        <item>65 to 69</item>
        <item>70 and older</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="budget_array">
        <item>$0 to $100</item>
        <item>$101 to $150</item>
        <item>$151 to $200</item>
        <item>$201 to $250</item>
        <item>$251 and above</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="coverage_array">
        <item>Cover for Hospital Bills</item>
        <item>Cover for Accidents</item>
        <item>Cover for Critical Illness</item>
        <item>Cover for Life</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="term_array">
        <item>Up to age 65</item>
        <item>Up to age 85</item>
        <item>Life Time Coverage</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="expense_array">
        <item>$0 to $500</item>
        <item>$501 to $1,000</item>
        <item>$1,001 to $1,500</item>
        <item>$1,501 and above</item>
    </string-array>

    //policiesPage strings
    <string name="content">image</string>
    <string name="browseByType">BROWSE INSURANCE POLICIES BY TYPE</string>
    <string name="type1">Critical Illness</string>
    <string name="type2">Disability</string>
    <string name="type3">Hospitalisation</string>
    <string name="type4">Accident</string>
    <string name="header">INSURANCE POLICIES</string>
    <string name="policyName">AIA Beyond Critical Care</string>
    <string name="policyDescription">
        Offers premium refund for 43 Major illnesses, relapse as well as mental illness. Comes with optional add-ons to cover upto 104 other illnesses.
    </string>

    //AboutUsPage strings
    <string-array name="aboutus_array">
        <item>Inquiry</item>
        <item>Quote</item>
        <item>Feedback</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    //homepage strings
    <string name="questionnaireText">FIND YOUR SUITABLE POLICIES!</string>
    <string name="latestNews">THE LATEST NEWS</string>
    <string name="newsTitle">NEW COVID-19 POLICIES</string>
    <string name="newsDesc">MULTIPLE INSURANCE COMPANIES NOW OFFER COVERAGE FOR HOSPITALISATION DUE TO COVID-19</string>

    //newsPage strings 1
    <string name="artTitle1">MAS reprimands AIA, Prudential and Aviva for breaching regulatory requirements</string>
    <string name="artShortDesc1">Insurance companies Aviva, AIA and Prudential have been found by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) to have breached regulations by not reviewing the performance of their supervisors and for paying them beyond the limit set by regulations.</string>
    <string name="artLongDesc1">MAS in a release on Tuesday (June 15) said that the companies have been reprimanded for the offences that happened between
        2017 and 2019. MAS has serious concerns regarding the misconduct and the financial institutions, and individuals are required to remediate the issues
        promptly.The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) found that three insurance companies did not review the performance of their supervisors. The
        firms also failed to assign the supervisors a grade as required under regulations. They paid commissions to these supervisors that exceeded the
        stipulated cap as well. The central bank has reprimanded these companies and two other individuals for the breaches. MAS has also directed Aviva
        Financial Advisers to appoint independent persons to conduct a review of its internal control processes </string>
    //string 2
    <string name="artTitle2">NTUC Income reimagines insurance to give control back to customers</string>
    <string name="artShortDesc2">The company(NTUC Income) introduced Singapore’s first rain insurance, Droplet, which protects customers against price surges on ride-hailing platforms during rainy days</string>
    <string name="artLongDesc2">As an insurtech player, Income has launched groundbreaking products that have enriched customers’ insurance experience. For instance, the company introduced Singapore’s first rain insurance,
        Droplet, which protects customers against price surges on ride-hailing platforms during rainy days by reimbursing 60 per cent of fares so that commuters could confidently hail rides. In support of the Singapore
        Green Plan 2030, Income recently partnered with car marketplace Carro, integrating the latter’s telematics capabilities and its dynamic pricing technology to launch Covered, a usage-based model where electric car
        drivers pay for motor insurance according to the mileage they drove. Income aims to insure all eligible electric vehicles to promote the adoption of green cars in the island-state.</string>

</resources>